<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zixiang&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>http://zxnie.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Zixiang&#39;s Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 14:30:29 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zxnie.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Simulate inband device-to-device communications underlay with cellular network with MATLAB</title>
      <link>http://zxnie.github.io/posts/d2d-pairing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 14:30:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zxnie.github.io/posts/d2d-pairing/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is a write-up of my course project for EEL6509: Wireless Communications, Fall 2018.
Device-to-Device (D2D) communication was initially proposed in cellular networks as a new paradigm to improve network performance. The emergence of new services such as content distribution and location-aware advertisement introduced new use cases for D2D communications in cellular networks. The initial studies showed that D2D communication has advantages such as increasing spectrum efﬁciency and reducing communication delay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perform DoS attacks on Software-defined Networking with mininet and ONOS</title>
      <link>http://zxnie.github.io/posts/ddos-on-sdn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 14:41:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zxnie.github.io/posts/ddos-on-sdn/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is a write-up of my course project for EEL6871: Software-defined Systems, Fall 2018.
This work is based on Varadharajan, Vijay, et al. &amp;ldquo;A Policy based Security Architecture for Software Defined Networks.&amp;rdquo; arXiv preprint arXiv:1806.02053 (2018). The project aiming to reproduce the work in the above paper and discuss how the security policies impact software-defined networking (referred as “SDN” in the rest part).
Policy based security architecture is wildly used in the conventional network: most firewalls following a set of policies to filter the flows going through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Stick Dash</title>
      <link>http://zxnie.github.io/posts/smart-stick-dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 13:41:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zxnie.github.io/posts/smart-stick-dash/</guid>
      <description>Smart Stick Dash</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>